http://www.betterbodiesyoga.com/privacy/

Skip to content
901-767-9642 | 692 West Brookhaven Circle, Memphis, TN
38117901-618-2878| 684 West Brookhaven Circle, Memphis, TN
38117
YOGA CLASSESYoga and its Benefits Class Schedule Yoga Q&A Testimonials
SALT SERVICESWhat is Halotherapy Salt Cave Q&A Salt Cave Policies Testimonials
PRICINGRegister Here Pricing & Policies Salt Bed Pricing & Policies
EVENTSBBY Gallery
ABOUT USOur History Our Instructors The Great Yoga Wall® Yoga Garden Salt Caves Media Contact
PROLONWhat is the Fast Mimicking Diet? Purchase Prolon Kit
Privacy Policy
Better Bodies Yoga is an East Memphis studio offering Hatha Yoga, established in 2004. Feng shui detail throughout, immaculate, peaceful and welcoming. Open seven days a week, numerous classes for every level student from beginner to advanced. All instructors are 200-hour and above YA certified who teach with attention to alignment and safety. We provide one free yoga class weekly specifically for individuals with cancer as well as their support persons in partnership with the Wings Foundation in the West Clinic Cancer Center. In addition to Hatha Yoga, we specialize in therapeutic yoga for injured, sport specific persons and special populations. Every class and private lesson ends with our special signature Savasana (final relaxation), comprised of a hot towel (cold in the heated classes) covering the eyes, and a shoulder and neck rub, and feet when time allows.
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (www.betterbodiesyoga.com). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 901-767-9642 or via email at karen@betterbodiesyoga.com
Go to Top
